To start off, you're going to look at a Python class I've written called Gaussian.
首先 我们来看看我写的一个 Python 类 叫做 Gaussian
Then, you're going to code this on your own.
然后你将自己编写该类
You can see that the class has an init method for instantiating an object.
该类有一个用于实例化对象的 init 方法
There are three attributes, mean,
里面有三个属性
standard deviation, and an empty list for storing data.
分别是均值 标准偏差和用于存储数据的空列表
Notice that the init function includes a default value of
注意在 init 函数里 均值的默认值为 0
0 for the mean and one for the standard deviation.
标准偏差的默认值为 1
This is like any other Python function where you
和任何其他 Python 函数一样
can specify default values for the inputs.
你可以指定输入的默认值
Notice as well the init has no input for the data attribute,
此外注意 在 init 方法里 data 属性没有输入值
a class attribute does not need to be included in the init input variables.
类的属性不是一定要包含在 init 输入变量中
Then, I've defined a handful of
然后我定义了其他方法
other methods to calculate the mean of the data for example here,
用于计算数据均值
the standard deviation of the data here,
计算数据的标准偏差
and a method to read in a data file called read data file.
以及读取数据文件的方法 叫做 read_data_file
There are a few other methods as well that we'll get to in a minute.
还有几个其他方法 稍后我会讲解的
Looking at the read data file method,
查看 read_data_file 方法后会发现
you can see that this method reads data from
该方法将从文件里读取数据
a file and then stores the data in the data attribute.
然后将数据存储在 data 属性中
There's something particularly interesting about the read data file method.
read_data_file 方法有个特别之处
This code actually calls the calculate mean and calculate standard deviation methods from
这段代码会调用 self 变量的 calculate_mean 和 calculate_stdev 方法
the self variable and then stores
然后将结果
the results in the mean and standard deviation attributes.
存储在 mean 和 stdev 属性中
The self variable not only gives you access to the class attributes,
self 变量不仅使你能够访问类属性
but also to the class methods.
而且能够访问类方法
The Gaussian class has a couple of other methods as well.
Gaussian 类还有几个其他方法
One plots a histogram using the matplotlib package.
其中一个方法使用 matplotlib 软件包绘制直方图
I've also included a function for outputting
还有一个函数会输出
the results of a probability density function and
概率密度函数的结果
a plot of a normalized histogram with
另一个函数会绘制归一化直方图
the probability density function in the same x value range.
并绘制在同一 x 值范围内的概率密度函数图
These are just to give more examples of how you can use class methods.
这些示例演示了如何使用类方法
Next, I actually use the class by instantiating an object called Gaussian one.
接下来 我将使用该类实例化一个叫做 gaussian_one 的对象
Here I'm going to run that code cell.
现在我将运行该代码单元格
Because I haven't specified any parameters,
因为我没有指定任何参数
the default mean and standard deviation are used.
因此将使用默认均值和标准偏差
There's a data file called numbers.txt in the same folder as this Jupyter Notebook.
Jupyter Notebook 所在的同一文件夹里有一个叫做 numbers.txt 的数据文件
So, I read in the data from that file and then use
我从该文件里读取数据
the other methods to output a couple of plots.
然后使用其他方法输出几个图形
In this next part of the lesson,
在这节课的下一部分
I'm going to give you a skeleton version of
我将给出该 Gaussian 类的框架版本
this Gaussian class with a few sections marked to do.
其中有几个部分标记为 TODO
This is what it looks like.
看起来是这样的
Your task is to fill out the code.
你的任务是填写代码
The code is already in this video you just went through,
视频里已经包含了答案代码
but try not to peep back at this video.
但是尽量不要偷看视频
Follow the comments in the to-do sections
请阅读 TODO 部分的注释
and see if you can code the Gaussian class on your own.
然后自己编写 Gaussian 类
The file you're going to work with also contains
你将使用的文件还包含单元测试
unit tests that you can run to help check your work.
你可以运行这些测试 检查代码是否正确
There at the bottom of the file,
它们位于文件底部
let me show you how that works.
我演示下操作方式
So, if you run this first code cell up here,
如果运行这里的第一个代码单元格
then you can execute this second code cell
那么会执行第二个代码单元格
and it'll show you the results of all the unit tests.
系统将显示所有单元测试的结果
It says that I have a few errors,
这里显示了几个错误
a few failed tests,
以及几个失败的测试
so, I need to go back and work on the code.
因此我需要重新修改代码
Writing code that you've already seen might seem like a silly exercise,
让你编写你已经见过的代码似乎有点傻
but it should help solidify your understanding of
但是有助于巩固
how object-oriented programming works in Python.
Python 面向对象编程知识
You'll work on a more challenging coding assignment at the end of the lesson.
在这节课结束时 你将完成一个更有挑战的编程任务
For now, see how much of the Gaussian class you can rewrite on your own.
暂时先看看自己能重新编写多少 Gaussian 类代码
But don't worry, I've also included an answer file as part of the code.
但是别担心 我还提供了代码的答案文件